hear?
聞こえる?
You're a shy person.
腰がりさんのね
Wow, it's coming out, it's all messed up.
すごい 出ちゃってる びちゃびちゃにしちゃったね
Did you feel much better?
い っぱい気持ちよくなった?
You'll lick me hard
一生懸命舐めてくれるね
Take off your shoes.
靴 脱ぐんだね
A lot of it came out, so it's all over my butt.
い っぱい出ちゃってたからお尻に塗れちゃってるね
Your butt will get better
お 尻よくなるよ
You like your butt warm, don't you?
お 尻温かいの好きでしょ?
Was it painful?
苦しかった?
Is it painful?
苦しいか?
painful
切ない
You have a face
顔 してるね
You're good at it
上 手だね
I got out because I'm good at it.
上 手だからさ、出ちゃった
Can I drink this?
これ 飲める?
this?
これ?
He drank it
飲んでくれた
Raise your eyes and look down
目 の上あげて 下の下見して
I let my spirit out, I can't let it in here.
精 神出しちゃった こっちに入れてないんだよ
what?
何?
outside?
外?
Let's find it outside
外 に見つけちゃおう
People might see you
人 に見られちゃうかもしれない
Look at it and think it feels good.
気 持 ち いいなって思って 見てね、
There are people
人いるよ
I want you to come all the time, but I also want to see Yumi's body.
ず っと来ててほしいけどさ や っぱりゆみちゃんの体も見たい
From now on
から ね
good ass
いい お尻
You have a really nice butt
本当 にいいお尻してるよね
Is it hard?
硬 いの?
yes
そう
I liked this earlier
これ さっき気に入ってたもんね
It's always there.
ず っとそれ入ってるね い
Yes, of course you like it, right?
っぱ い入れたもん そうだよ、もちろん 好きでしょ、
That kind of thing
そういうの
Your body is hot, your body is sagging.
体 熱いね 体つぶってるね
Can't you do well with that?
それ 入ってて上手くできないの?
Does it feel that good to have it in there?
それ入っててそんなに気持ちいいの?
I just feel bad
気さしたばっかりになる
Does it feel good?
気 持ちいい?
I'm tired, so cute
疲れちゃった かわいいね
Does it feel good?
気 持ちいい?
it hurts?
痛い?
Let's do something different
違うやつにしよう
It won't fall. It's okay. Cute. Cute?
落 ちないよ 大丈夫 かわいい かわいい?
Kneeling Yes, kneeling
膝立ち そう 膝立ち